<Document>
# Phaethon Dynasty Lore Summary

[bold][color=#636B2F]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] is a defiant imperial state born from the ruins of history’s most ruthless powers.
Once seperatist states erected from the [color=yellow][bold]First and Last Corporate War[/color][/bold] that fell to Trans-Solarian Federation occupation at the edge of inhabited systems, [bold]The Colossus Sector[/bold] became a
crucible of survival, unity, and technological advancement. Here, a populace left scarred from a foreign reigime, corporate war survivors,
and [bold]Syndicate[/bold] remnants built something new
a Dynasty of the discarded, fiercely independent and violently opposed to the oppresive regime
of the [bold][color=cyan]Trans-Solarian Federation (TSF)[/bold]

<Box>
[bold][color=#636B2F]“Erected from ashes. Forged in the abyss.”[/color][/bold]
</Box>

Emerging from the wreckage of the [color=yellow][bold]First and Last Corporate War[/color][/bold], [bold][color=#636B2F]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] holds deep ideological
scars. Its people are the children of war, and betrayal.
Many are the children of [bold][color=#8B0000]Syndicate[/bold][/color] remnants who once served shadowy economic overlords, now pledge allegiance the Phaethon Dynasty, the decendents of the last [bold][color=#8B0000]Syndicate[/bold][/color] commanders.
They are united by a shared hatred of foreign states and a vision of an isolationist empire.
The Dynasty is not perfect; torn between old world [bold][color=#8B0000]Syndicate[/bold][/color] ideology and new idealists,
funded by black markets, and surviving on salvaged tech.  though small, its industrial and technological, and military complex rivals that of large enemy forces. Its culture of asymmetrical warfare and geographical advantages make it nearly impossible to crush.


Guerrilla strikes, AI corruption, propaganda floods, and sabotage operations leave the TSF
scrambling to take control of [bold]The Colossus Sector[/bold]. Their tactics are as much ideological as they are military. With neural
leaks, anti-propaganda broadcasts, and liberated mythologies, [bold][color=#636B2F]The Phaethon Dynasty[/bold][/color] spreads rebellion in the Federation like a virus. Their space stations scattered across the colossus remain off every map, hidden from the eyes of foreign powers
- Bastions of myth, and legends. To the Dynasty peace will never come through treaties.
Only through collapse — the total dismantling of the systems that forgot them.

<Box>
[bold][color=#636B2F]“Thrash against the machine, Destroy the regime.”[/bold][/color]
</Box>


</Document>
