<Document>
# Roleplay Rule 8
## Certain areas are designated as Safe Zones.

Some locations, such as the Colonial Outpost (CO) and Medical Dispatch (MD), are [color=green]recognized safe zones[/color]. The Safe Zone is defined as the area within a 256 meter radius around the point of interest (POI), with the POI's center as the originating point. Hostile actions (striking, raiding, etc.) against these areas or within this radius are [color=red]never allowed[/color], regardless of shift duration.

Stealing from others is also prohibited within Safe Zones. However, possession of contraband is still illegal, and you can be searched and arrested for contraband even while inside a Safe Zone.

[color=yellow]Clarifications:[/color]
- If you have a bounty, are part of an antagonistic faction, or are seeking shelter in a Safe Zone to avoid consequences, you may still be arrested or detained by security or authorities. Safe Zones do not grant immunity from arrest or investigation, only from being killed on sight (KOS).
- Ongoing fights or hostilities do not magically end when someone enters a Safe Zone. Attempting to abuse Safe Zones to escape consequences or disrupt roleplay may result in administrative action.
- [color=yellow]If an attempt to arrest or detain someone in a Safe Zone escalates into violence, all parties should prioritize non-lethal outcomes.[/color] Gunfights and lethal force should be avoided; focus on running, detaining, or using non-lethal means. Escalating to deadly violence in Safe Zones is strongly discouraged and may result in staff intervention.

[color=green]Safe Zones exist to provide a secure environment for roleplay, medical treatment, and new player orientation. Violating Safe Zone rules may result in administrative action.[/color]

- Safe Zones: Colonial Outpost (CO), Medical Dispatch (MD), and a 256m radius around their centers.
- No hostile actions, including but not limited to: attacking, raiding, seizing control, or stealing from others.
- These restrictions apply at all times, with no exceptions.
- Possession of contraband is still illegal and may result in arrest, even within a Safe Zone.
</Document>